<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Escape Harm in Healthcare]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Escape Harm in Healthcare]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/safetylee/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 20:29:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/safetylee/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 20:29:21 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SafetyLee]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FJ5Wx4245RQw%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DJ5Wx4245RQw&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FJ5Wx4245RQw%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxdkTFvwjAQhff8CpfFidQ46URRAgOiK1M3hCrLPqKgxg6-C2oE_PfaGIWq0_nuvXv65Ktf8pxtXNuzPF8lNSr_JEZjD8sZwQ8VR3mWcTpbJYydpWNfWp3YMpbrle321VPAKGAQLrcghE5IpexgyIt8vpiX5ds7rxIvpofBKGqtSTN28X3M0cobtVVDB4aEciAJPr4hdCmPMDyr7natRIANwf9weRVEiaMJaeQGmDbQhREvCpKNaIC09wtlu-LBJo7Iq4kG_8J494ME1-OnbLaygyfTrtzHPRS9dN60tRpEaxAcreFgHaRavTK8w9-y1Ne6iMv-88MpwOjpHL-PgH7J" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/J5Wx4245RQw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9f85c9d9-41c2-4cdd-ad6c-c95746a4fed9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 16:02:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Your Health Insurer Doesn't Care About Your Big Bills - ProPublica]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/d47150a3e25a51b69d055e50440f5133/noop.jpg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fassets.propublica.org%2Fimages%2Farticles%2F20180525-michael-frank-insurance-og.jpg%3F1527238815"><h1>Why Your Health Insurer Doesn&apos;t Care About Your Big Bills - ProPublica</h1><p>Michael Frank ran his finger down his medical bill, studying the charges and pausing in disbelief. The numbers didn&apos;t make sense. His recovery from a partial hip replacement had been difficult. He&apos;d iced and elevated his leg for weeks. He&apos;d pushed his 49-year-old body, limping and wincing, through more than a dozen physical therapy sessions.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safetylee/why-your-health-insurer-doesnt-care-about-your-big-bills-/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5f40ae3e-fd05-48bb-9b9a-315f0b9d5bbb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 17:11:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process Street]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/4396e98ae387204e147d5e641a37e7e2/noop.jpg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fs3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fbolin%2Ffront-street%2Fprocess-street-promo.jpg"><h1>Process Street</h1><p>Process Street is the home for your team&apos;s recurring tasks. Create, track and optimize business process workflows.</p></article>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxdkTFvwjAQhff8CpfFidQ46URRAgOiK1M3hCrLPqKgxg6-C2oE_PfaGIWq0_nuvXv65Ktf8pxtXNuzPF8lNSr_JEZjD8sZwQ8VR3mWcTpbJYydpWNfWp3YMpbrle321VPAKGAQLrcghE5IpexgyIt8vpiX5ds7rxIvpofBKGqtSTN28X3M0cobtVVDB4aEciAJPr4hdCmPMDyr7natRIANwf9weRVEiaMJaeQGmDbQhREvCpKNaIC09wtlu-LBJo7Iq4kG_8J494ME1-OnbLaygyfTrtzHPRS9dN60tRpEaxAcreFgHaRavTK8w9-y1Ne6iMv-88MpwOjpHL-PgH7J" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://app.process.st/checklists/jh8i1VcR3TOnxwZmSGRBvg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7e0a27d4-d24f-48a2-a3df-a23a140a7957</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 10:50:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJx1jrEOgjAURXe-4tq9bZSJpGUxJO58QWkfESKU9D2N_L0xJG6O5547HHfSGr2EIsgjbs-h37KgWwZKuOZE0LqtAMexTJtA9o28EnqLncMrHKvClLy6sz5QP3JIVBQC72tEopEKuESvrJ3Z_H5sYl5sfWnqc1ObmVXr7GHayn2zujX9j_oAB_874Q" height="900"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJx9UL3OwjAM3HkKk93NjloYPjF-E09gEkODyI9ig-DtaWgZWPB0Ovl85-vXiHBQqgr5BP_MGtJZYB-P7OHgaigKiNsVTNP7cAd3JZHBxGUTw6lSZHQ5KYXE1YAnJZTqBjOqFtlYS6V04-0oJWvncrQfsZ2k0Z5ZsQHMCeMTHV05eao7bhkGrTc2295O3ksKmVPps_BglB9qL3SnmTXwZSxKGlw3ypRgwYnVft58f2n58U38Zc_dRZrpfLT59q2nffI_W3oB7ihy_g</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">39ba5fe4-f50d-4701-ada4-bb904111a2df</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 17:53:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Refund Policy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Refund Policy</h1>,<p>1. <strong>Terms</strong> By accessing the website at https://techspeare.com or https://safetylee.com, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.</p>,<p>2. <strong>Use</strong> License Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Techspeare Pte Ltd's website for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: modify or copy the materials; use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial); attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Techspeare Pte Ltd's website; Remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Techspeare Pte Ltd at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.</p>,<p>3. <strong>Disclaimer</strong> The materials on Techspeare Pte Ltd's website are provided on an 'as is' basis. Techspeare Pte Ltd makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Techspeare Pte Ltd does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.</p>,<p>4. <strong>Limitations</strong> In no event shall Techspeare Pte Ltd or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Techspeare Pte Ltd's website, even if Techspeare Pte Ltd or a Techspeare Pte Ltd authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.</p>,<p>5. <strong>Accuracy of materials</strong> The materials appearing on Techspeare Pte Ltd's website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Techspeare Pte Ltd does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete or current. Techspeare Pte Ltd may make changes to the materials contained on its website at any time without notice. However Techspeare Pte Ltd does not make any commitment to update the materials.</p>,<p>6. <strong>Links</strong> Techspeare Pte Ltd has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Techspeare Pte Ltd of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user's own risk.</p>,<p>7. <strong>Modifications</strong> Techspeare Pte Ltd may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.</p>,<p>8. <strong>Governing Law</strong> These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Singapore and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.</p>,<p><strong>Privacy Policy</strong> Your privacy is important to us. It is Techspeare Pte Ltd's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Techspeare Pte Ltd may change this privacy policy from time to time at Techspeare Pte Ltd's sole discretion.</p>,<p><strong>Pre-order Safety Refund Policy </strong>Please note that, given the nature of the challenge we seek to address in patient safety, no refund will be possible and you agree to accept the online service provided ‘as is’, irrespective of the function or value it may provide.</p>,<p><strong>Curate Safety Refund Policy </strong>Please note that, given the nature of the challenge we seek to address in patient safety, we expect you to work with us (Techspeare Pte Ltd and our AI application SafetyLee) to successfully prevent harm in healthcare and you will only be refunded if we are successful in using your inputs in preventing harm to others as determined by Techspeare Pte Ltd. No refund will be possible for any other reason whatsoever and you agree to accept that this determination will be made at the sole discretion of Techspeare Pte Ltd or its panel of experts as the case may be.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safetylee/terms-of-use-privacy-policy-and-refund-policy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03cb4e72-c4a6-47bb-bc3b-334cc5d11779</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 15:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxdjkEOgyAQAL9C9gGigkUb8S8gSyGFYgBD0te3aW8eZy4zq7dZRSTNm-ok3FgPxKF_uCqBLRxIybsEV-tR7pS21rqzYEgpdnuKFKNGQ-088mFRs50GwbletOiZQGZHwfikZgPk19ApG8wSvoWG-umrCiE1e4ZQ9oz4IjG9r-rC20r_v9sHuTU-_w" height="750"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxdjkEOgyAQAL9C9gGigkUb8S8gSyGFYgBD0te3aW8eZy4zq7dZRSTNm-ok3FgPxKF_uCqBLRxIybsEV-tR7pS21rqzYEgpdnuKFKNGQ-088mFRs50GwbletOiZQGZHwfikZgPk19ApG8wSvoWG-umrCiE1e4ZQ9oz4IjG9r-rC20r_v9sHuTU-_w</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">04a8f5fe-8305-49c6-ad53-af78c2927cd8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 19:39:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJx1jrEOgjAURXe-4tq9bZSJpGUxJO58QWkfESKU9D2N_L0xJG6O5547HHfSGr2EIsgjbs-h37KgWwZKuOZE0LqtAMexTJtA9o28EnqLncMrHKvClLy6sz5QP3JIVBQC72tEopEKuESvrJ3Z_H5sYl5sfWnqc1ObmVXr7GHayn2zujX9j_oAB_874Q" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJx1jrEOgjAURXe-4tq9bZSJpGUxJO58QWkfESKU9D2N_L0xJG6O5547HHfSGr2EIsgjbs-h37KgWwZKuOZE0LqtAMexTJtA9o28EnqLncMrHKvClLy6sz5QP3JIVBQC72tEopEKuESvrJ3Z_H5sYl5sfWnqc1ObmVXr7GHayn2zujX9j_oAB_874Q</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">398a2e4c-c66e-4dc3-8b85-f72209f59b14</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 18:54:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Termly]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwljzGOgzAQRXtOMWsppTGEDWEjcJMrpNnSsYdgrWGssQni9hsl5XvF0__9l5RwQ57DDjc29s8vD7iSQ5BSF0XvRzYzwuZdngZRV9VBQMp7wEFM6B9TvsDP6Tm9JNuXyjmmi1ImxjK_o6Un5ciuMy5ZRfZPY3cZKXi7KzzWlWuaVtrzyclv047SnDsrm8a0Td3VbYdHAe8Bd2KHPIhKgAmBtnENIVlGXHQB0Ef9SyvDnWlLyOAIEyyUIa0xEmf4vEhlr6IuevVB_Q8RuVKl" height="244"></iframe>,<article><h1>Privacy Policy</h1></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/safetylee/termly/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7d6375f3-e8fe-4494-bd83-d71f1c3e93c7</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 15:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>